Seino, Galgal Channel, Go!
Yes, so today we're all eating candy and NG words!
Maybe we're all together too much.
I wonder if anyone has played this game before?
Maybe a few times?
But we gathered together as if we had never played this game before.
I don't know.
But it was like that.
But if I tell you now, you'll find out.
They would find out.
That's true.
That sounds difficult.
I'll make them say it. I'll lead them on.
So we can talk about it.
That's true.
That's for sure.
Yes, I'm sure.
Wow, that's scary.
I have a feeling we're going to a great place.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's go for it.
Let's make up our minds.
Let's start the video!
This time, I'm wearing T-Holic's costumes.
Then, I can wear them.
Bye bye.
I wonder.
I wonder what she's going to say.
It's a lie.
I wonder.
But, you know, to get that word out.
I like what you've been saying lately.
Anything recent?
Lately?
Anything warm?
Oh, that's nice.
Warm and fuzzy?
Warm, warm, warm.
Warm, then.
I'll go with warm.
What are you gonna say?
But, uh...
What's wrong? We're just talking.
I'm about to say something stupid.
I don't know.
But I say miiin and miiin and miiin a lot.
I write it in my voice.
I'm pretty sure it's miiin, but...
He writes in his voice.
Isn't that bad?
Miiin...
Miin says a lot of things.
Miin says it a lot.
But the camera's rolling.
I'm like, "Is this Miiin?
Sometimes he suddenly says "I".
That's good.
Mii, I'm going to go for it.
Mii?
Mii.
I'll go next.
Where do you want me to go next?
Okay, then.
In 8 days.
Oh, really?
Absolutely.
But on the other hand...
He might be leery.
He might even say it.
I'll say it.
Really?
On the other hand, it might be over soon.
On the contrary.
You're right.
Do it the other way around.
Crackle!
Yes, sir.
I'm off then.I'm off then.
What is it, Mi-chan?
I don't know.
I guess so.
It's really nice.
And it's so subdued.
I know.
Yeah.
Will it work?
I think it'll work.
You think it'll work?
Two or three.
It's one of those things, right?
You're a jerk.
I didn't tell him.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What a pain in the ass.
It's all jammed up in here.
Yeah, you're just gonna pull it out?
What a jerk.
That's right.
Now that we have all the snacks, let's get started with the NG words!
I can't talk.
Well, let's have a toast if it's all right.
Cheers!
Cool!
A little more!
Let's eat!
Can't you talk like this?
What?
Isn't it great? It's well-directed.
I wonder what it says.
Let's eat.
Bon appétit.
Your favorite.
Which one do you want first?
I'm curious about this one.
I want some eclair.
I don't eat it.
That's right, because NG is.
Because if you eat it, you're at a disadvantage.
What are you guys up to these days?
Lately, you know, work.
Yeah, but everyone's working hard.
But we're all working pretty hard, taking lessons and stuff.
Lots of lessons.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Good morning. Isn't it awfully warm?
Good morning.
It's warm.
You're warm.
Uh-oh.
Wait a minute. There's someone who doesn't talk at all.
I'm sorry. What's wrong?
I'll talk.
What's with this tone?
It's like you're trying to be sexy.
I'll talk. I don't understand.
So, how are you doing? Recently.
You're doing large numbers, right?
It's difficult, isn't it? I guess.
The cherry blossoms are blooming.
Who's going? Cherry blossom viewing?
I wish I could go.
But, you know, I often pass by the office and it's in bloom.
But there are a lot of insects.
It makes me sad.
Bugs.
My back.
Everyone's body shrinks now.
They have a lot more body.
They're hunched over.
I'm sorry, but we're all going to eat.
Let's talk.
So, what I want to do this year, this spring.
This spring.
What I want to do this spring.
I'm going to be a college student.Because I'm going to be a college student.
I'm going to be a college student.
I want to challenge myself a lot, don't you?
Hmmm.
It's rare that we don't have a conversation like this when the two of us are together.
Hey. Hey, listen, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Kinoshita-san talks a lot, doesn't he?
That's for sure.
Yoko.
But Momochan's graduating, too,
Oh yeah.
I can do a lot of things.
That's for sure.
Kaboron already.
Unexpectedly.
Well, it's the same, isn't it? I guess so.
So you can concentrate on your work.
Aiming to be the president.
I've said that many times, haven't I?
You're pretty serious.
Both in words and phrases.
That's right.
It's important.
Yes.
Spring.
The two of us.
But I might want to go see cherry blossoms.
Oh, that's exactly what I mean.
We haven't really done hanami before.
That's for sure.
In private.
Crawling.
But lately, when I organize my photos, I might forget.
The point is.
I see.
I usually look at clothing websites.
So, do you have any idea what colors you want this season, or what kind of clothes you're looking for?
But it's spring.
Yes, yes, yes.
Spring?
What?
It's spring.
It's going to be like this.
Pastel colors.
Summer is expensive.
Recently, there's a sound like a cell phone notification.
I like to type on the keyboard while I can hear it.
What? Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock?
But it sure feels good.
It's delicious.
There's cream in it.
I don't think I'm supposed to say this. I don't think we're going to tell each other.
I don't think so.
It's kind of difficult.
We'll just have to talk about it some more.
I agree.
What about the future of Girls Girls Girls?
What's the concept?
It's something.
Just normal.
What kind of activities do you want to do, what do you want to work on?
Sweepus is working hard on dancing and singing right now.
We are taking a lot of dance and singing lessons right now.
Yesterday, I had a great talk with the vocal teacher.
Really?
How to be good at it.
That's a good thing. By the way, what did you write down when you asked me how to get better?
What did you write? Let's see, this is how you do it, Cape-chan.
Hmmm... But I thought, well, you are a very hardworking person.
I value individuality.
So I hope you can find a way to practice that suits you.
Recently, everyone is doing self-study.
That's right.
You know what I mean?
Not so much.
You mean it didn't open from here? You mean it opens from behind?
I think I'm going to go.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't know. I'm not feeling very strong today.I don't know, I'm not feeling very energetic today.
Oh, I'm not putting any energy into it.
I'm going to go...
Ehhhh...
Bravo!
I don't like it.
Women who are too strong aren't popular.
Oh, my God.
Yes, no, Rina Tan.
You're so cool.
I don't have it on me.
Thank you.
It's normal.
I'll just say what I usually think.
I'll tell you what I'm thinking.
I'm thinking about what's going on in the gallery.
on YouTube and all the old stuff on YouTube.
I think we've all become so much prettier.
I think they've become so cute!
I also think that Yocho is getting prettier.
Everyone's getting prettier.
Well, if you want...
Um...
I really don't know about you, but...
I think Kira-chan's face has gotten really tiny
Even more so.
I mean, you were always tiny to begin with, but...
I'm really tiny
I don't know, I really don't know
I changed my hair color.
It's like I've changed my impression.
Originally, it was like this
Now it's like this.
But I used to be
Swollen
As I grew up
As I grew up, the swelling increased.
But I thought maybe it's something I corrected.
Uh, maybe.
But you didn't take them out.
No, I didn't.
If I did, you know...
That's when the color starts.
Suddenly.
I'm sure.
I didn't pull it out.
It's all settled.
He's forcing her to change her mouth.
What, you're not gonna tell him to rub it in?
I do! It was on the schedule.
Three days later.
I saw it. I saw it.
What's this all about?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm just saying it's not a good idea... but it's a little too much... so I'm here at the conclusion.
I'm sure you're right.
I'm sure he'll say something like that.
I'm sure he'd love to be your guide here. Like, "Take that off." Like, "Okay.
"Okay"?
Oh, my God, this is it.
It's okay.
Okay?
No, that's too mean.
Okay, you guys, stop using the word "mien" and start talking.
Okay.
I'll talk.
Oh, this one comes in a variety of flavors.
You like Warehouse?
Yeah, I do.
Vanilla.
You like vanilla?
Do you like vanilla?
You don't really say that.
I mean, Mie, not just Mie, but me too.
Kiyo, I said it once.
Oh, I'm saying it here?
Yeah.
It's like you're having a conversation right now.
Yeah, and... Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. - Okay.
Okay, then.
Okay.
Oh, it's so tight.
I noticed right away that Momochan was blaming you.
Really?
Later.
That was close.
Yeah.
What about Kira?
I see.
Wait, by the way...
By the way...
Who decided on "Momoseyanai"?
Who decided?
I don't know.
I thought it was either...
Then I saw a lot of patterns of Momochan's "Momo Seyan na na".
I don't know, it's like, here we are...
Here we are... here we are...
I can't believe it.
Repertory
And, oh my...
I can't believe it.
That was so serrated.
That's why you were smiling so much when you came in.
Yeah.
That's a tough sell.
Yeah, it is.
You were saying it was pretty good.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Didn't I?
Did you get it?
Wait a minute, I clapped.
No, I didn't.
Do it again.
You said a lot, didn't you?
Subtle.
It's a triangle.
But, you know, you were saying this.
Triangle.
It's funny.
continue
Sankaku-ton
The pork was terrible!
Triangular dragon
It makes me laugh.
Kira is so fragile.
Broken or something?
Usually funny
Asia Comics
Can I talk?
Ah, power.
What?
pi
Minamikoshi
I'm sorry.
You're mean, aren't you?
That's not right.
You're so mean!
I already said it.
What do you mean?
I've already said it.
What's the right answer?
Well...
I'm serious.
He's not talking, so I'm just thinking.
But I don't want to say what I just said.
You just said...
Uh-huh.
Like...
I was mmm...
If you look into your feelings...
before that.
There was a kind of ummmI had a "hmmm" moment.
First.
I told you.
When I said what I said...
I was like...
I was just checking.
I knew it!
Yuka, you can be out too.
I'm out too.
What is it?
Speak up.
It's a triangle.
You talked.
I see.
Kilo what?
Tell me.
I'll make him say it.
What?
Really, what?
I'm glad you get it when I give you a compliment.
No, it's not.
What?
No, it wasn't.
I knew it.
I was gonna tell you.
Oh, yeah.
Let's do the first one.
The first what?
The first time.
Let's not say it.
Momo, first time.
Yuka, the first time...
What?
I didn't.
I lied.
Momo attacked.
You have the best face.
That's what I really think.
I'm serious.
Mi.
I've only done it once.
I'll go tell him.
Yuuka is warm
Talking about spring
Clothes...
How are you?
Spring
I thought I'd say it's because it's warm
It's all about fashion.
I don't say that at all.
It's hard to say "it's warm.
It was hard, wasn't it?
It took me so long to say it.
And that's that.
Thank you for watching!
If you like this video
If you liked this video, please leave a high rating, a good button, or subscribe to our channel.
Leave a comment
I'm doing it again
High rating, channel subscribe, comments
If you liked this video
High rating, channel subscribe, comment
please do so.
See you soon!